localecanada.com 2014-06-09

# Locale Canada

_Last Updated January 8, 2013_

Locale Canada LLC (the “Company”, “we” or “us”) operates LocaleCanada.com (the “Site”) and related mobile software (the "Software"), and other affiliated products and services (collectively, the “Services”). This Privacy Policy applies to all users of the Services and describes the Company’s collection and use of users’ personal information (e.g., information that identifies a specific person, such as full name or email address), and non-personally identifiable information (e.g., device information and usage) to the extent such information is associated with a particular user or user account.

**Your use of the Services signifies that you agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, do not use the Services.**

The Services are general audience, are not targeted to children, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 years of age. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from a child under age 13, please contact us at [privacy@localecanada.com](mailto:privacy@localecanada.com?subject=Locale%20Canada%20Privacy%20Policy).

## **COLLECTION OF INFORMATION**

### **_User Submitted Information_**

**Personal Information You Submit.** When contacting us for issues or creating a user account related to the Services, you may submit personal information (such as your full name, e-mail address, and other identifying information) to allow us to respond to your inquiry. Your submission is voluntary and you have the choice not to disclose any information to us. In addition, when you install the Software on your mobile device, you may be asked to allow us access to certain information on your device, including your address book, contact data information, location, SMS messages, SD card contents, and other system tools. If you do not want us to have access to this information, please do not install or use the Software.

**Public Information and Posts.** Reviews, comments or content that you may voluntarily post on or through the Services, information about you that accompanies those posts or content, such as a user name and/or user picture, as well as personal information that you may provide in your user account profile (such as your full name, e-mail address, and other identifying information), will be publicly available to anyone, and will be displayed in search results both on the Services and on external search engines and sites.

**Third Party Information and Content.** If you access the Services using a third party service, connection or log-in, your user submitted information may also include your user name associated with that third party service, any information or content you have permitted the third party to share with the Company, and any information you have made public in connection with that third party service. Such third party information and content will be governed by this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service, and may be publicly available according to applicable policies and user permissions granted by you. In addition, the Company may supplement user submitted information with other information we collect or obtain from third parties.

### **_Collected Information_**

**Accessing and Using the Services.** When users access or use the Services, certain non-personally identifiable information is collected, stored and used for business and marketing purposes, such as maintaining and improving the Services, conducting research, and displaying more relevant advertisements. This non-personally identifiable information includes, without limitation: IP address, unique identifier number, operating system, browser information, URLs visited, pages viewed, search queries entered, and other software and hardware information. If you access the Services from a mobile or other device, we may collect a unique device identifier assigned to that device or other information for that device in order to serve content to it. This collected data may also be supplemented with information obtained from third parties or submitted by users.

**Tracking and Data Collection Technologies.** The Company may use browser cookies, web and DOM storage data, Adobe Flash cookies, pixels, beacons, and other tracking and data collection technologies, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. These technologies may be used to collect and store information about your use of the Services, including without limitation, web pages, features and content you have accessed, search queries you have run, referral URL information, links you have clicked on, and advertisements you have seen. This data is used for business purposes such as providing more relevant ads and content, and market research. The Company may also use these technologies and other similar tools to relate your use of the Services to personal information obtained from you or a third party. For example, cookie, click stream or other data about your activities using the Services may allow us to limit the content provided to you through the Services to items we think you will find interesting and relevant to you, based on your prior online activities and preferences.

**Third Party Tracking and Data Collection.** Third parties that support the Services by serving advertisements or providing other services, such as tracking aggregate site usage or providing users with the ability to comment on or share content, may also use cookies, pixels and other tracking and data collection technologies described above to collect user information. The Company does not control these third parties and their use of these technologies is governed by the privacy policies of the third parties using such technologies.

For more information about third party ad networks that use these technologies, see <http://www.aboutads.info/>. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, but you can change your settings to notify you when a cookie is being set or updated, or to block cookies altogether. Please consult the "Help" section of your browser for more information (e.g., <http://windows.microsoft.com/en-US/windows-vista/Block-or-allow-cookies>).

Users can manage the use of Flash technologies, including cookies, with the Flash management tools available at Adobe's website at the following link - <http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html>.

Please note that by blocking cookies or implementing other restrictions, you may not have full access to the Services or certain features thereof.

## **USE & DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION**

We only share your non-public personal information with non-affiliated third parties when we believe sharing is permitted by you or authorized by this Privacy Policy. In addition, the Company may share your personal information with our parent, subsidiary or affiliate companies without restriction.

Any information about users that we collect or receive may be used and shared with others as follows:

**To provide and manage the Services.** We use the information we collect from and receive about users to provide the Services to you, to measure and improve the Services, to personalize your experience by delivering relevant content, advertising, and marketing messages, to allow you to comment on content, to enable you to communicate and share with other users or services, and to provide you with customer support and respond to inquiries. We may use aggregated, anonymous data about use of and activity on the Services to assist us in this regard and such data is not subject to this Privacy Policy.

**To allow third party service providers to assist us in providing and managing the Services.** The Company may make your non-public personal information available to certain third party service providers, such as contractors, agents or sponsors, who help us manage or provide the Services. Examples of such services include, without limitation: advertising and marketing, developing or supporting products and features, administering message boards, processing data or statistics, or supplementing or organizing information and data. 

**To contact you.** The Company may periodically send promotional materials or notifications related to the Services to the email address you may have provided to us or periodic alerts on your mobile device if requested by you. If you want to stop receiving promotional materials from the Company, follow the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each promotional email or other method of notification. There are certain service notifications and emails that you may not opt-out of as long as you are registered with or subscribed to the Services, such as notifications of changes to the Services or policies.

**To deliver relevant advertising.** We may use the information you provide to us, and information we collect about your use of the Services through tracking and other technologies, to assist us in delivering you relevant ads and content when you use the Services. We may work with third party advertising networks and advertisers who help deliver these ads to you. We may share non-personally identifiable information (such as search queries you have run, referral URL information, links you have clicked on) or aggregated information with third parties to improve the relevancy of the ads and content you see using the Services. As noted above, these third party advertising networks and advertisers may also use cookies and other technologies to collect and track non-personally identifiable information such as demographic information, aggregated information and Internet activity to assist them in delivering advertising that is more relevant to your interests. They may also utilize supplemental data from other sources and analytics methods to help deliver more relevant ads. To find out more about third party online advertising and to opt out of this type of advertising, visit the following websites:

Digital Advertising Alliance: <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>

Network Advertising Initiative: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

**To protect the rights of the Company and our users.** There may be instances when the Company may disclose user information without providing notice or choice, including situations where the Company has a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary in order to: (i) protect or defend the legal rights or property of the Company, our affiliated companies, or any of their employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements); (ii) protect the safety and security of users of the Services or members of the public; (iii) protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or (iv) comply with the law or legal process.

**To complete a merger or sale of assets.** If the Company sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of its assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or transfer of all or a material part of its business, the Company may transfer your information to the party or parties involved in the transaction as part of that transaction.

## **NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES**

This Privacy Policy is the means by which the Company provides you with notice about its collection and use of your personal information. The Company may modify this Privacy Policy at any time, and each such modification will be effective upon notice to you (including posting on the Site). All material modifications will apply prospectively only. It is therefore important that you review this Privacy Policy regularly. You may also receive a copy of this Privacy Policy by emailing us at [privacy@localecanada.com](mailto:privacy@localecanada.com?subject=Locale%20Canada%20Privacy%20Policy). 

## **THIRD PARTY SERVICES**

The Services include links to and advertise third party sites, services or products, including without limitation online stores, rewards programs, trial offers, newsletters, contests or sweepstakes. The Company is not responsible for the privacy practices of any such third parties, and once you click on an advertisement or link, you should review the applicable privacy policy of the third party service or site.

## **LOCATION**

The Services are hosted in the United States and the Company is based in the United States. If you are a user located outside of the U.S., you understand and consent to having any personal information you provide transferred to, processed, and stored in the U.S. and other countries where data protection and other privacy laws may not offer the same level of protection as in your jurisdiction, such as the European Union. This includes the use of cookies and other tracking technologies as described above.

## **INQUIRIES AND CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy or wish to request information pursuant to California Civil Code Section 1798.83, please contact us at [privacy@localecanada.com](mailto:privacy@localecanada.com?subject=Locale%20Canada%20Privacy%20Policy).
